<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on PK Flyer</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on PK Flyer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Settle Down</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/music/2023-settle-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/music/2023-settle-down/</guid>
      <description>2 songs documenting a gentle breakout of lockdown mindsets, floating lightly on the soft joy of creative collaboration.&#xA;1st song is imaginary. 2nd song is about a real town in Illinois where my family went to Church, and my father worked as a welder for a short time on a now decommissioned nuclear power plant on Lake Michigan.&#xA;Recorded on January 29th, 2022&#xA;Credits Composed by: Paul Karner Performed by: Emma Hospelhorn, Brian Sulpizio, John Sutton, Andrew Trim, Seth Vanek, and Paul Karner Engineered and mixed by: Drew Durepos &amp;amp; Alex Inglizian Mastered by: Mikey Young </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halo Machine</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/music/2023-halo-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/music/2023-halo-machine/</guid>
      <description>Halo Machine was composed atop 3 separate drones. The songs use religious tropes to explore the meditations and brooding that comes with the monastic rhythms of living alone during lockdown.&#xA;Liner Notes Halo Machine Just keep scrolling.&#xA;Lake Street There’s a presumption that you have to get out of the city to find peace and tranquility, but for me the stretch of Lake St between Ashland and Kedzie has always been a place of respite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mira</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/music/2024-mira/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/music/2024-mira/</guid>
      <description>CREDITS Engineered and mixed by Brian Sulpizio&#xA;All songs written and arranged by** Paul Karner**&#xA;Performers:&#xA;Becca Shorr&#xA;Stuart Seale&#xA;Kimberly Sutton&#xA;Dani Simandl&#xA;Chihsuan Yang&#xA;Brian Sulpizio&#xA;Paul Karner</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
